A Guide to the Papers of R. Smith Simpson, 1919-1981
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of R. Smith Simpson 1918-1991
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
2897-k
This collection consists of ca. 225 items (3 Hollinger boxes.)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The Honorable Robert Smith Simpson, Annandale, Virginia, gave these papers to the Library on May 7, 1992, through Kenneth Jensen, Acquisitions Department.
Scope and Content Information
This addition to the papers of former diplomat R. Smith Simpson (1906- ) contains ca. 225 items (3 Hollinger boxes), 1918-1991, consisting of Christmas letters, bound printed material concerning the activities and writings of Simpson, an oral history interview with Simpson, and committee records, including newsletters, memoranda, and minutes of the Committee for the Study of Diplomacy.
Contents List
- Christmas Letters from the Simpsons 1952-1990 (Box 1)
- Committee for the Study of Diplomacy 1969-1990 (Box 1)
- Committee for the Study of Diplomacy (UVA Set) 1969-1989 (Box 1)
- Oral History Interview with R. Smith Simpson 1991 May 13 (Box 1)
- Personnel Records: Activities, Set No. 2 (Incomplete) 1931-1966 (Box 1)
- Personnel Records: Activities, Set No. 2 1967-1991 (Box 2)
- Personnel Records: Published Writings, Set No. 2 1918-1951 (Box 2)
- Personnel Records: Published Writings, Set No. 2 1952-1977 (Box 3)
- Personnel Records: Published Writings, Set No. 2 1978-1991 (Box 3)
- Report of the Committee on the Textile Industry in the United States of America 1937 Apr (Box 3)